=== 160 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7861915?gh_jid=7861915
TITLE: Senior Corporate and Policy Communications Manager (12 Month FTC)
LOC: Paris, France
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: Are you passionate about driving the success of a global business in the dynamic and fast-paced world of corporate communications? If so, we have the perfect opportunity for you! As the Corporate Communications Manager for France, you will play a central role in shaping and executing the communications strategy for one of the biggest markets for Airbnb globally. The ideal candidate is a self-starter and a 

=== 161 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7737620?gh_jid=7737620
TITLE: Homes Supply Growth Manager
LOC: Sydney, Australia
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: Hosts are our brand and enable amazing travel experiences for our guests. The mission of the Homes Supply team is to make hosting appealing, rewarding and easy. We are building capabilities that allow us to recruit and retain hosts at a global scale. The Difference You Will Make: As Growth Manager based in Sydney, you will be responsible for the growth and scaled acquisition of high-quality hosts and homes

=== 162 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7917632?gh_jid=7917632
TITLE: Audiovisual Infrastructure Engineer
LOC: San Francisco, CA
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: Our team builds, operates and maintains AirbnbÆs global video production and large-scale audiovisual infrastructure in our event spaces, collaboration hubs and large specialty conference rooms at offices around the world. We work closely with the Infrastructure builds team, the live production crew and the office of the CEO to deliver highly functional and reliable AV infrastructure. The Difference You Wil

=== 163 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7859591?gh_jid=7859591
TITLE: Engineering Manager, Checkout (Booking & Pricing)
LOC: United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Checkout team is a critical team within the Booking & Pricing (B&P) organization. Booking & Pricing has a wide array of mission critical responsibilities across the Guest and Host experience including merchandising listings, enabling Booking and Reservation Management and managing pricing & calendar systems. As the Engineering Manager for Checkout, you will lead the team responsible for AirbnbÆs Checkout online APIs and user exper

=== 164 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7760751?gh_jid=7760751
TITLE: Head of Homes Supply, Southeast Asia
LOC: Bangkok, Thailand
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: The Homes team is responsible for growing AirbnbÆs destination business and growing the supply ensuring we maintain a competitive portfolio of Accommodation listings that meet guest expectations for value, variety, and experience. The team also supports hosts globally by enabling efficient planning and execution of growth strategies that align with AirbnbÆs mission and resonate with local communities. The 

=== 165 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7731737?gh_jid=7731737
TITLE: Senior Technical Program Manager, Payments
LOC: Bangalore, India
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: AirbnbÆs mission is to create a world where people can Belong Anywhere. As we grow to achieve that mission, weÆre looking to add a technical, hands-on, and mission-driven Technical Program Manager (TPM) to support the Payments and Insurance Engineering team. This person will partner with our Payments and Insurance engineering, ops, and product teams to build new Payments and Insurance capabilities and deli

=== 166 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7566181?gh_jid=7566181
TITLE: Specialist, Premium Support
LOC: Japan
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Difference You Will Make: We are seeking a dedicated and enthusiastic candidate to provide exceptional Customer Service support to the Airbnb community as a CS Specialist, Premium Support. The ideal candidate is hospitable, analytical, and committed to delivering the highest standards of service. This is a full time position based in Japan. The CS Specialist, Premium Support functions on the front line interacting directly with bo

=== 167 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7821110?gh_jid=7821110
TITLE: Growth Marketing Lead, Korea
LOC: Seoul, Korea
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The community you will join At Airbnb, the Growth Marketing team sits at the dynamic crossroads of marketing, engineering, and data science. WeÆre responsible for driving AirbnbÆs business performance by deploying innovative, data-driven marketing strategies. The difference you will make As Growth Marketing Lead, you will help shape AirbnbÆs growth strategy in Korea by identifying opportunities, generating insights, and partnering wit

=== 168 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7535063?gh_jid=7535063
TITLE: Market Associate
LOC: Paris, France
REGEX: False / associate title
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: Our Supply Team is growing, and we want you to be part of it! As a Market Associate, you will play a crucial role in the retention, growth, and optimization of host entrepreneurs and rising hosts in your assigned territory. These hosts are individuals who manage their own property or support owners by hosting on their behalf. You will focus on building strong relationships with these hosts, helping them op

=== 169 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7902817?gh_jid=7902817
TITLE: Systems Engineer, BizTech(Python, LLM, GenAI, MCP)
LOC: Bangalore, India
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. Systems Engineer Airbnb | India Airbnb has built a global platform that connects travellers and hosts across 34,000 cities, offering more than two million listings worldwide. We run mission-critical enterprise systems that operate around the clock across all time zones. These systems are essential to enabling our teams to work efficiently and productively. As our Business Technology organization continues to expand, we are seeking hig

=== 170 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7782435?gh_jid=7782435
TITLE: Senior Manager, Product & AI Policy
LOC: United States 
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: In Community Policy, our mission is to create and evolve principled policies that establish the rules of the road for guests and hosts across Airbnb. This involves solving some of the most complex Trust & Safety challenges of our time. Our work is informed by rigorous research and stakeholder collaboration, and we design policies that can support our community at scale. We team with our cross-functional pa

=== 171 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7904319?gh_jid=7904319
TITLE: Field Sales Intern, EMEA Services
LOC: Barcelona, Spain, Milan, Italy, Paris, France
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The community you will join: Airbnb is seeking Field Sales Interns to join the EMEA Services team for a 6-month internship. Just like Airbnb disrupted hospitality, Airbnb Services is redefining the guest experience by bringing premium in-home services directly to Airbnb stays. Airbnb Services offers 10 categories (chefs, photography, massage, personal training, nails, etc.) across 280 cities, with new offerings and locations dropping 

=== 172 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7874555?gh_jid=7874555
TITLE: Gestionnaire, Soutien α la sΘcuritΘ
LOC: Canada
REGEX: False / no ec or technical signal
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. Airbnb a pris le jour en 2007 lorsque deux H⌠tes ont accueilli trois invitΘs dans leur maison de San Francisco, et compte depuis lors plus de 4 millions d'H⌠tes qui ont accueilli plus d'un milliard d'invitΘs dans presque tous les pays du monde. Chaque jour, les H⌠tes proposent des sΘjours et des expΘriences uniques qui permettent aux invitΘs de se connecter de maniΦre plus authentique aux communautΘs. La diffΘrence que vous ferez : _*

=== 173 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7936532?gh_jid=7936532
TITLE: Lead, Advanced Analytics, Services
LOC: United States
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: Airbnb, a global leader in the travel and hospitality industry, is dedicated to creating a world where anyone can belong anywhere. With our unique accommodations and experiences, we connect travelers with local hosts across the globe. As we continue to innovate and grow, we're looking for dynamic individuals to join our team and help shape our trajectory. The Difference You Will Make: Airbnb is seeking a L

=== 174 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7944544?gh_jid=7944544
TITLE: Field Sales Associate, Services
LOC: Mexico City, Mexico
REGEX: False / no ec or technical signal
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. This opportunity is offered as a 12-month fixed term contract. The Community You will Join: The Supply organization plays a pivotal role in driving AirbnbÆs growth and expansion efforts worldwide. This team recruits and develops AirbnbÆs global supply of high-quality Services. By focusing on quality supply and international expansion, the team leads the way for AirbnbÆs continued growth and the facilitation of millions more host and g

=== 175 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7554915?gh_jid=7554915
TITLE: Staff Fullstack Software Engineer, Marketing Technology
LOC: Remote - USA
REGEX: False / staff-level
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: Our mission at Marketing Technology is to provide a state-of-the-art platform and measurement capabilities to enable marketing and product teams to engage with our customers effectively. Everyday millions of Airbnb customers are reached via our streamlined platform over comprehensive channels, such as Email, Push, SMS, and external Ads Platforms (e.g., Google, Facebook, etc). We deliver substantial busines

=== 176 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/6717690?gh_jid=6717690
TITLE: Staff Experience Designer
LOC: United States
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The community you will join: As a Staff Experience Designer, you will partner with supporting disciplines such as writers, researchers, product specialists and engineers to build beautiful, usable, forward-looking products that empower people. Our design charter is to help foster an emotional connection with our community, keeping usability and accessibility as our prime virtues. We do our best to practice inclusive design at every tu

=== 177 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7895517?gh_jid=7895517
TITLE: Manager, Luxe Supply
LOC: Canada
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Difference You Will Make: As the Luxe Market Manager Field Manager for NAMER and LATAM, you will lead the team of on-the-ground market experts responsible for growing Airbnb LuxeÆs supply across North America, Latin America, and the Caribbean. You will set the strategy, coach the team, and own the results ù ensuring Airbnb Luxe continues to expand its portfolio of extraordinary homes while maintaining the quality standards that de

=== 178 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7642249
TITLE: Sr. Software Engineer, ML Platform, tvScientific
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 179 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7923203
TITLE: Sr. Data Scientist, GenAI & Labeling Platforms
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 180 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494960
TITLE: Engineering Manager II, Enterprise AI Solutions
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 181 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7075176
TITLE: Manager II, Machine Learning Engineering, Core Engineering
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US;  Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 182 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7927139
TITLE: Sr. Client Partner
LOC: Amsterdam, NL
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 183 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7782571
TITLE: Software Engineer II, ML Platform, tvScientific
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 184 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7927431
TITLE: Integrated Marketing Manager
LOC: Singapore, SG
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 185 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7859359
TITLE: Sr. Client Account Manager, CPG
LOC: Chicago, IL, US
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 186 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7836254
TITLE: Sr. Client Account Manager, Retail (Italian Market)
LOC: Dublin, IE
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 187 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7239260
TITLE: Manager II, Machine Learning-Search
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 188 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7525112
TITLE: Group Product Manager I, Connections
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 189 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7747116
TITLE: Staff Product Designer, Patterns & Design Innovation
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US;  Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 190 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7682058
TITLE: Sr. Client Account Manager
LOC: Sydney, AU
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 191 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=5572858
TITLE: Sr. Software Engineer, Backend
LOC: Toronto, ON, CA
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 192 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7770914
TITLE: Security Software Engineer II, Detection and Response
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 193 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494921
TITLE: Vendor Security Analyst
LOC: Chicago, IL, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 194 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7869925
TITLE: Lead Client Partner Retail / e-Commerce
LOC: New York, NY, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 195 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7684660
TITLE: Sr. Staff Engineer, Performance Ad Formats
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 196 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6087213
TITLE: Sr. Data Scientist, Core
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 197 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7682052
TITLE: Sr. Client Partner
LOC: Sydney, AU
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 198 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7642265
TITLE: Software Engineer II, Simulation, tvScientific
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 199 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7787615
TITLE: Lead Client Partner, Tech
LOC: New York, NY, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 200 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=5132899
TITLE: Software Engineer II, Backend
LOC: Toronto, ON, CA
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 201 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494708
TITLE: Sr. Security Software Engineer, Application Security
LOC: Chicago, IL, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 202 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7789148
TITLE: Client Account Manager II, CPG
LOC: New York, NY, US
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 203 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7816431
TITLE: Security Software Engineer II, Security Operations
LOC: Chicago, IL, US; Remote, US
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 204 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6121464
TITLE: Sr. Machine Learning Engineer, Core Engineering
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US; Seattle, WA, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 205 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7890197
TITLE: Lead Product Analyst, Pinner Engagement
LOC: New York, NY, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 206 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7782563
TITLE: Sr. Software Engineer, Simulation, tvScientific
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 207 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7663075
TITLE: Sr. Lead Client Partner, Financial Services
LOC: New York, NY, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 208 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7832348
TITLE: Staff Software Engineer, Batch Processing Platform
LOC: Seattle, WA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / staff-level
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 209 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6121543
TITLE: Machine Learning Engineer, Monetization Engineering
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US; Seattle, WA, US
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 210 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6483186
TITLE: Sr. Client Account Manager
LOC: Singapore, SG
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 211 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494938
TITLE: Sr. Machine Learning Engineer, Responsible AIû Applied Research Science
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, CA, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 212 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7434494
TITLE: Senior Channel Lead, Marketing Sites
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 213 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7871244
TITLE: Go-to-Market Strategy & Insights Lead
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 214 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7808602
TITLE: Agency Lead
LOC: Chicago, IL, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 215 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7681666
TITLE: Machine Learning Engineer II
LOC: Dublin, IE
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 216 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7903948
TITLE: Lead Client Account Manager, Mid-Market
LOC: Chicago, IL, US
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 217 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7507652
TITLE: Sales Finance Analyst II
LOC: Dublin, IE
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 218 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494917
TITLE: Staff Software Engineer, Conversion Data Privacy
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / staff-level
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 219 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7752846
TITLE: Manager II, Machine Learning Engineering-Homefeed
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 220 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7685105
TITLE: Sales Finance Manager I
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Chicago, IL, US; New York, NY, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 221 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7642251
TITLE: Sr. Data Scientist, tvScientific
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 222 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7495002
TITLE: Lead Industry Manager - Partner Sales
LOC: Singapore, SG
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 223 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6121551
TITLE: Sr. Machine Learning Engineer, Monetization Engineering
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US; Seattle, WA, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 224 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7276167
TITLE: Sr. Sales Manager, DE Emerging Verticals
LOC: Hamburg, DE; Berlin, DE; Munich, DE
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 225 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7782229
TITLE: Principal Engineer, Online Systems
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 226 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6819404
TITLE: Staff Data Scientist, Engagement Ecosystem
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / staff-level
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 227 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7946155
TITLE: Sr. Client Account Manager (12 Months Fixed Term)
LOC: Melbourne, AU
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 228 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7678730
TITLE: Lead Program Manager, Global SMB Vendor Operations
LOC: Los Angeles, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 229 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7255640
TITLE: PhD Fall Machine Learning Intern (ATG ù Visual, Multimodal, and Recommender Systems)
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US; Seattle, WA, US; New York, NY, US
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 230 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7770918
TITLE: Sr. Staff Software Engineer, Merchants
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 231 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494562
TITLE: Technical Accounting, Manager I
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 232 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7904689
TITLE: Integrated Marketing Specialist
LOC: London, UK
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 233 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7743636
TITLE: Sr. Product Designer, Measurement & Conversion
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 234 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7678754
TITLE: Lead Client Partner, Tech & Telco
LOC: Seattle, WA, US
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 235 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=6121450
TITLE: Machine Learning Engineer, Core Engineering
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US; Seattle, WA, US; Remote, US
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 236 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7494765
TITLE: Staff Machine Learning Engineer, Programmatic Ads
LOC: San Francisco, CA, US; Palo Alto, CA, US; Seattle, WA, US
REGEX: False / staff-level
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 237 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7435596
TITLE: Staff Data Scientist, Monetization
LOC: Toronto, ON, Canada
REGEX: False / staff-level
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 238 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7426610
TITLE: Manager II, Engineering
LOC: Toronto, ON, CA
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

=== 239 ===
URL: https://www.pinterestcareers.com/jobs/?gh_jid=7641112
TITLE: Sr. Client Account Manager, Travel
LOC: New York, NY, US 
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: About Pinterest: Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, weÆre on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product. Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each otherÆs unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? ItÆs Possible. At Pinterest, AI isn't just a feature, it's a powerful partner that augments our creativity and amplifies our impact, and weÆre looking for candidates who are excited to be a part of that. To get a complete picture of your experience an

