=== 0 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7557909?gh_jid=7557909
TITLE: [2026] Software Engineer, Game Developer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: True / explicit ec technical
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Software Enginee

=== 1 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7832171?gh_jid=7832171
TITLE: Director of Public Policy, UAE/Middle East
LOC: Remote
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As the Director of ME

=== 2 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7813041?gh_jid=7813041
TITLE: Localization Program Manager
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WeÆre seeking a detai

=== 3 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7473686?gh_jid=7473686
TITLE: [2026] Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Account Identity - PhD Early Career
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WHY SAFETY? At Roblox

=== 4 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7733855?gh_jid=7733855
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Co-Experience
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Frontend Enginee

=== 5 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7904238?gh_jid=7904238
TITLE: Head of Education Policy, Government & Global Impact - India and South Asia
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Based in India, the H

=== 6 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7886349?gh_jid=7886349
TITLE: Support Escalations Specialist
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Support Escalati

=== 7 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7283870?gh_jid=7283870
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Client Systems (C++)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As Senior Software En

=== 8 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7561736?gh_jid=7561736
TITLE: Core Engine Developer - Systems (C++)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Engine Networking

=== 9 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7897876?gh_jid=7897876
TITLE: Critical Harms Investigations & Incident Management Specialist
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / no ec or technical signal
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. RobloxÆs Safety Opera

=== 10 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7831044?gh_jid=7831044
TITLE: Social Media Analyst
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Social Media Ana

=== 11 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7684162?gh_jid=7684162
TITLE: Editor
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As an Editor, you wil

=== 12 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7716688?gh_jid=7716688
TITLE: Lead/Senior Lead, Roblox Incubator Program
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. We are seeking a Lead

=== 13 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7896061?gh_jid=7896061
TITLE: Senior Security Software Engineer, Infrastructure Security
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Security 

=== 14 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7655813?gh_jid=7655813
TITLE: Tech Lead Manager (TLM) - Ads Experience
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. With RobloxÆs daily a

=== 15 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7909802?gh_jid=7909802
TITLE: Marketing Manager, LATAM
LOC: Sπo Paulo, Brazil
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. We are seeking a vers

=== 16 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7931525?gh_jid=7931525
TITLE: Senior Detection and Response Engineer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. About the role: As a 

=== 17 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7788918?gh_jid=7788918
TITLE: Senior Brand Designer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Roblox is looking for

=== 18 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7616345?gh_jid=7616345
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Are you a seasoned en

=== 19 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7923586?gh_jid=7923586
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer - Release
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Software 

=== 20 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7839207?gh_jid=7839207
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer, Crash Reporting
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Principal Softwa

=== 21 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7309267?gh_jid=7309267
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Engine Systems
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Software 

=== 22 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7776654?gh_jid=7776654
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer - Safety Experience
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WHY SAFETY? At Roblox

=== 23 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7903021?gh_jid=7903021
TITLE: Senior Analyst, AI Workflows & Automation
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As an AI Workflow Spe

=== 24 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7931896?gh_jid=7931896
TITLE: Engineering Manager - Creator Business
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. What YouÆll Do: As an

=== 25 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7819841?gh_jid=7819841
TITLE: Senior Product Manager, Avatar Movement
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. About the Role: As a 

=== 26 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7932208?gh_jid=7932208
TITLE: Principal/Senior Product Manager, Communications
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. About the Role: The C

=== 27 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7740354?gh_jid=7740354
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer, Stateless Jobs Platform (Core Services)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Core Services tea

=== 28 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7779304?gh_jid=7779304
TITLE: [2026] Design & Creative Fellowship
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Design & Creative

=== 29 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7816258?gh_jid=7816258
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Compute Cell Platform
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a senior software 

=== 30 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7528070?gh_jid=7528070
TITLE: Senior Mobile Systems Engineer, Audio Team (Android & C++)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. You Have: Experience:

=== 31 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7923268?gh_jid=7923268
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Avatar Animation
LOC: Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As Senior Software En

=== 32 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7514942?gh_jid=7514942
TITLE: Senior Risk Data Analyst
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Risk Data

=== 33 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7848812?gh_jid=7848812
TITLE: Senior Data Scientist, Engine Systems
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WHY DATA SCIENCE & AN

=== 34 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7185278?gh_jid=7185278
TITLE: Senior/Principal Platform Engineer, ML Platform
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. ML Platform powers hu

=== 35 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7565086?gh_jid=7565086
TITLE: Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Alt Defense
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WHY SAFETY? At Roblox

=== 36 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7682993?gh_jid=7682993
TITLE: Principal AI/ML Engineer, Reliability
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Why Reliability? Robl

=== 37 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7808950?gh_jid=7808950
TITLE: Senior Product Manager - Consumer Platforms (Web & Backend)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Consumer Platform

=== 38 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7411636?gh_jid=7411636
TITLE: Principal Data Scientist - Safety
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WHY DATA SCIENCE & AN

=== 39 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7894481?gh_jid=7894481
TITLE: Scientist / Senior Scientist, Ads Systems
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. WHY DATA SCIENCE & AN

=== 40 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7323437?gh_jid=7323437
TITLE: [2026] Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Multimodal AI, Computer Vision and Graphics - PhD Early Career
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior keyword
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. At Roblox, computer v

=== 41 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7913706?gh_jid=7913706
TITLE: Video Editor
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Video Editor at 

=== 42 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7569608?gh_jid=7569608
TITLE: Senior Engineering Manager - Risk & Fraud
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. What YouÆll Do: As an

=== 43 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7651420?gh_jid=7651420
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer - Engine Reliability
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Software 

=== 44 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7605764?gh_jid=7605764
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer, Cluster Lifecycle
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Principal Softwa

=== 45 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7940279?gh_jid=7940279
TITLE: Engineering Manager - Account Security
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Account Security 

=== 46 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7409707?gh_jid=7409707
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer - Matchmaking
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Software 

=== 47 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7838662?gh_jid=7838662
TITLE: General Manager, South East Asia
LOC: Singapore
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. About the Role Roblox

=== 48 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7543730?gh_jid=7543730
TITLE: Learning and Coaching Partner
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Learning and Coac

=== 49 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7758770?gh_jid=7758770
TITLE: Senior Product Counsel, Safety
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As Product Counsel, S

=== 50 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7392981?gh_jid=7392981
TITLE: Product Policy Specialist
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Product Policy Sp

=== 51 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7744272?gh_jid=7744272
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Every day, tens of mi

=== 52 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7826403?gh_jid=7826403
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Developer Monetization (Fullstack)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Developer Monetizatio

=== 53 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7793685?gh_jid=7793685
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer - Studio Architecture
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Sr. Studio Softw

=== 54 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7561743?gh_jid=7561743
TITLE: Principal Engine Programmer - Systems (C++)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Engine Networking

=== 55 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7793925?gh_jid=7793925
TITLE: Senior Workday Compensation Engineer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The People, Places, a

=== 56 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7473601?gh_jid=7473601
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer - Game Engine Systems
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Engine Networking

=== 57 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7702696?gh_jid=7702696
TITLE: Senior Finance Business Partner, G&A
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As an early Senior Bu

=== 58 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7841812?gh_jid=7841812
TITLE: Developer Engagement Representative - Indonesia (Part-Time Contract)
LOC: Remote
REGEX: False / ec but non-technical title
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The Developer Relatio

=== 59 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7862734?gh_jid=7862734
TITLE: Senior Design Program Manager
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Design Pr

=== 60 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7926169?gh_jid=7926169
TITLE: Developer Relations Manager (UAE)
LOC: Remote
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Developer Relati

=== 61 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7859569?gh_jid=7859569
TITLE: Senior Fullstack Software Engineer, Social Play
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Senior Software 

=== 62 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7535858?gh_jid=7535858
TITLE: [SkillBridge] Information Security Fellowship
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / ec but non-technical title
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. This training program

=== 63 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7785852?gh_jid=7785852
TITLE: Analyst, Vendor Assurance & Compliance
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / no ec or technical signal
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As an Analyst, Vendor

=== 64 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7792862?gh_jid=7792862
TITLE: Workforce Management Analyst
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Workforce Manage

=== 65 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7813127?gh_jid=7813127
TITLE: Salesforce Engineer
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior experience required
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. We are seeking a dyna

=== 66 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7769510?gh_jid=7769510
TITLE: Principal Software Engineer - Creator Collaboration
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Roblox Studio is the 

=== 67 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7809292?gh_jid=7809292
TITLE: Senior Product Manager - Consumer Platforms (Consoles)
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. About the role: The C

=== 68 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7779120?gh_jid=7779120
TITLE: Product Counsel, Advertising
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As Product Counsel fo

=== 69 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7629843?gh_jid=7629843
TITLE: Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Embodied AI and Smart NPCs
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. As a Principal Machin

=== 70 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7783533?gh_jid=7783533
TITLE: Product Support Specialist, International
LOC: Gurugram, Haryana, India
REGEX: False / no ec in requirements
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. RobloxÆs Safety Opera

=== 71 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7698330?gh_jid=7698330
TITLE: Senior Software Engineer, Service Mesh
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Who We Are: Roblox is

=== 72 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7595328?gh_jid=7595328
TITLE: Director of Engineering - AI for Roblox Studio
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Why Roblox Studio? Ro

=== 73 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7351059?gh_jid=7351059
TITLE: Senior Machine Learning Infrastructure Engineer, Ads
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. With Roblox Ads busin

=== 74 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7889259?gh_jid=7889259
TITLE: Critical Harms Investigations & Incident Management Specialist
LOC: Remote; San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / no ec or technical signal
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. RobloxÆs Safety Opera

=== 75 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7719252?gh_jid=7719252
TITLE: Principal App Store Manager
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / non-tech
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. The App Store Manager

=== 76 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7617984?gh_jid=7617984
TITLE: Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Content Safety
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Why Content Safety? A

=== 77 ===
URL: https://careers.roblox.com/jobs/7913665?gh_jid=7913665
TITLE: Director of Product, Consumer Frontend
LOC: San Mateo, CA, United States
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiencesû all created by our global community of developers and creators. At Roblox, weÆre building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device. WeÆre on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there. A career at Roblox means youÆll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone. Roblox users expect a

=== 78 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7417294?gh_jid=7417294
TITLE: SpΘcialiste, SΘcuritΘ
LOC: Canada
REGEX: False / no ec or technical signal
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. Airbnb a pris le jour en 2007 lorsque deux H⌠tes ont accueilli trois invitΘs dans leur maison de San Francisco, et compte depuis lors plus de 4 millions d'H⌠tes qui ont accueilli plus d'un milliard d'invitΘs dans presque tous les pays du monde. Chaque jour, les H⌠tes proposent des sΘjours et des expΘriences uniques qui permettent aux invitΘs de se connecter de maniΦre plus authentique aux communautΘs. La diffΘrence que vous ferez : On

=== 79 ===
URL: https://careers.airbnb.com/positions/7453190?gh_jid=7453190
TITLE: Senior iOS Automation Engineer
LOC: Brazil - Remote
REGEX: False / senior/management
DESC: Airbnb was born in 2007 when two hosts welcomed three guests to their San Francisco home, and has since grown to over 5 million hosts who have welcomed over 2 billion guest arrivals in almost every country across the globe. Every day, hosts offer unique stays and experiences that make it possible for guests to connect with communities in a more authentic way. The Community You Will Join: The Quality Engineering team helps Airbnb build high-quality software efficiently. We enable Airbnb engineers to build highly testable systems by building and using tools leveraging AI. We own and continuously improve product test cases, automation coverage, test automation tools, environments, frameworks. We navigate AirbnbÆs massive codebase identifying weak spots, and help design and implement testable 

